gul.com 2013-05-20

# Gul Privacy Policy - Gul Watersports Ltd

  * [Home](http://www.gul.com/ "Home") / 
  * About us /
  * Gul Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Gul Watersports Limited ("Gul") will always try to protect your privacy, the privacy Policy outlines what we may do with any data that we receive from you. Gul collects customer information to inform our customers about the Gul brand, products, services and promotions. We collect information including your name, e-mail and postal address that you provide to us when you register. We also monitor our site use and traffic patterns to improve our web site design and the products and services we offer. Gul recognises that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly.

Gul utilises the latest in secure server software (SSL) to ensure that all personal information, including credit card details, remains private and secure. Gul will not rent or sell your e-mail address or personal details for any reason. Customer confidentiality is our highest priority.

**Data Collection from you**

When registering your information with us, either when purchasing or signing up to the news letter you consent to Gul sending correspondence regarding the website and our stores to the e-mail address that you have registered. We would like to use your details to inform you of any promotions that we have running online and/or in our stores and on occasions send any catalogues that we produce. We would ask you when you register if you would like to receive this information. You can remove your email and postal address from our list at any time. There are links in the emails we send you or alternatively, you may e-mail us at info@gul.com or call us on +44 (0)1208 262 400.

Gul complies with the Data Protection Act 1998.

**Cookies how they are used**

As with most website we use cookies to collect data. Cookies are small data files that are temporarily stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. The Gul website uses cookies to help Gul to track patterns of behaviour that visit our site, which means we can offer you a better service and more improved browsing and shopping experience. Cookies are also used on the site to track contents of your shopping basket and products and contents that you select.

**Personal Data. How it is stored**

Personal data that you supply to us is stored on our secured server. All data is stored in the UK and we take all necessary steps to make sure your data is kept secure in line with the privacy policy.

**Contact**

Please feel free to contact us at any time should you have any questions regarding any of the above mentioned. You can e-mail us at info@gul.com or call us on +44 (0)1208 262 400.
